WINNIE AMONG Web Developer

Kampala , Uganda +256-762-278-266 w.among2023@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

During my internship in software engineering, I've been thrilled by the ever-changing world of technology. I've experienced a journey filled with excitement, entering the dynamic field of software development. Here, innovation, teamwork, and striving for excellence are key.

SKI		
51/7	므	-

Python Object oriented development	Agile software development
⊘ HTML	⊘ Teamwork
⊘ CSS	⊘ PostgreSQL
⊘ Git	✓ Test driven development
	Human Centered Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Bank of Uganda intern

Web Developer | 07 November, 2023 - 2024 March

- · Worked on bug fixes and improved system performance, resulting in a
- 10% increase in user satisfaction scores
- Applied Agile Methodology Skill in the development process
- Collaborated with a team in the development of a Transport Request System using software.

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

Transport Management system

Web Developer | November, 2023 - March, 2024

Built a high-performing web application to increase data efficiency

Be real motors spare parts company

Web Developer | 25, June 2023 - August, 2023

• Created a web application for efficient and sustainable record system for the sale of spare parts which was an in house system

EDUCATION:

2023 - 2024 | Refactory Academy Uganda

Certificate in Software Engineering - Software Engineering

REFRENCES